Guide to the Pool Family Papers, 1930-2000
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Pool Family papers 1930-2000
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Pool family.
20 linear feet Extent: 15000 Items
The Pool Family, including James Christopher and Elizabeth Pool and their three children, were Southern Baptist missionaries based in Nigeria, Liberia, and Texas between 1935 and the late 1970s. The collection also includes materials about foster children that they sponsored. Collection includes correspondence, printed materials, administrative records, photographs, and writings documenting the life and activities of the Pool family, particularly J.C. and Elizabeth Pool, and their lives as Southern Baptist missionaries to Nigeria and Liberia in the mid-20th century. The materials are especially relevant to the history of the Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary and the Pools' work with the Baptist community in Nigeria.
RL.01033
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Pool Family Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2011.
Historical Note
The Pool Family Papers consist of documents collected by Baptist missionaries J.C. (James Christopher, also Christie) and Elizabeth Pool and their relatives. J.C. was born Jan. 26, 1905 and earned an undergraduate degree from Baylor University in 1929 (after having been ordained in 1928) and a graduate degree from Southern Baptist Theological Seminary. Elizabeth was born July 17, 1909, earned an undergraduate degree at the Baylor College for Women (subsequently Mary Hardin-Baylor College and the University of Mary Hardin Baylor) in 1930, and taught at the San Marcos Baptist Academy from 1930-1932. After both traveling to Nigeria as missionaries in 1934, they were engaged and married in 1935. They had three children--Frances, born 1937, Carolyn, born 1940, and James (Jim), born 1945--and adopted two Nigerian children, Gordon Buraimo Pool, born 1934, and Claribel Olubunmi Alanke Pool, born 1931.
The Pools became key figures in the Baptist missionary community of Nigeria, primarily through their work at the Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary (where J.C. was principal) but also at the Ogbomosho Day School and the Baptist Mission Hospital, among other institutions. While in Nigeria Elizabeth published several books, including The Hill Called Moon (1944), Lucille Reagan of Africa (1954), and The Bead-Maker’s Son (1957). They were stationed in Liberia from 1971-1972 before retiring to San Angelo, Texas due to J.C.’s health problems. J.C. died Jan. 21, 1978, and Elizabeth died Nov. 13, 2000.
Notable family members include Elizabeth’s brother Ross Routh, a Brigadier General in the U.S. Army and Elizabeth’s father, Eugene Coke Routh, who served as the editor of the Baptist Messenger from 1928-1943 and the editor of the Commission (published by the Foreign Mission Board of the Southern Baptist Convention) from 1943-1948 and published a number of books on religious subjects.
In addition to these, relatives who are frequently mentioned in the Pool Family Papers include J.C.'s and Elizabeth's children and grandchildren: daughter, Frances Elizabeth Pool Haaren (also known as Frances Blinn, married Robert (Bob) H. Blinn, married John Haaren) and her children, Robert (Bobby), married Mary Beth; Keith, married Laura; Katherine, married Russ Allison; and Eugene (Gene), married Ruth. Another daughter of J.C. and Elizabeth was Carolyn Pool (also known as Carolyn Pool Bullington, married Richard Lunson Bullington, Jr.); her children were Richard, Jr., Margaret, Susan, Brenda, and Lillie. The Pools' youngest child, James (Jim) Christopher Pool, Jr., married Mary and had a son, James (Jimmy). The Pools also corresponded frequently with their two adopted children, Gordon Buraimo (who married Mary and had several children) and Claribel Olubunmi Alanke (who married Jonathan Ojeleye and had two children, Funlayo and Molara). Other relatives frequently mentioned in the Papers include J.C. Pool's mother, Mrs. U.H. (Etta) Pool; his siblings and in-laws, Albert and Josephine Pool; his aunt, Fannie Pool Lancaster; J.C. Pool's cousin, Wade Hill Pool; Elizabeth Pool's parents, E.C. and Alice Routh; her siblings and in-laws, including W.W. (Walter Wendell) and Leila K. Arnett, Clinton and Lucile Burnett, Copass and Loretta Routh, Porter and Ruth Routh, and Ross and Fay Routh; and her aunts and uncle, Katie Wrol House and B.B. and Leila Routh McKinney.
Friends and colleagues frequently mentioned in the Papers include Ruby Cooper, W.A. Criswell, Jessie Ford, Cornell Goerner, Osadolor (Osad) and Yewande Imasogie, Burton and Margaret (Margie) Lindan, Charles Maddry, Kathleen Manley (Man), Charles Martin, Hugh and Vera Peterson, Lucille Reagan, Josephine (Jo) Scaggs, William R. Tolbert, Jr., and Carl and Enid Whirley.
Collection Overview
The collection is divided into 8 series, each listed below with detailed descriptions. The largest series in the collection is the Correspondence Series, which consists of letters sent to and by the Pool family and their relatives, friends, and colleagues. It ranges from 1928-1998 with some undated materials, and with a gap in coverage from 1963-1968. Notable events and correspondence are described in the Collection Contents, roughly divided by decade.
The Photographs and Artwork Series includes both professional photographs from the Division of Visual Education at the Foreign Missions Board of the Southern Baptist Convention, along with personal portraits and snapshots taken by the Pools of both family and Nigerian scenes. The artwork present in this series consists of a set of watercolor prints with scenes of Liberia, created by Swedish artist Roland Svensson and published in 1969.
Family Writings includes J.C. Pool's autobiographies; J.C. Pool's sermon notes and writings, including his doctoral dissertation, addresses, historical essays, and many undated sermons; Elizabeth Pool's writings, including a draft of her book, autobiographical notes, and various poems, articles, and essays; E.C. Routh's writings; and other works collected by the Pools.
J.C. Pool's Teaching Materials include syllabi, student papers, and other materials, largely related to his career as a teacher at the Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary. A related series is the Missionary Materials Series, which also includes NBTS administrative and management documents, such as meeting minutes, founding documents, as well as materials from related organizations such as the Southern Baptist Convention's Foreign Missions Board.
The Family Papers Series includes the family's legal documents, financial accounts, a small amount of genealogy and family history materials, and a significant amount of memorial materials from the death of J.C. Pool in 1978. Family travel documents have been removed to the Travel Series, which also includes tickets, postcards, immigration materials, and other memorabilia from the many trips taken by the Pools.
Finally, the Printed Materials Series includes clippings, pamphlets and programs, magazines saved by the Pools, and reports about the Nigerian government and politics.
Subject Headings
Pool Family; Pool, J.C. (James Christopher); Pool, Elizabeth Routh; Routh, E.C. (Eugene Coke); Routh, Ross; Pool, James (Jim); Pool, Frances Elizabeth; Pool, Carolyn; Nigeria -- History -- 20th century; Nigeria -- History -- Civil War, 1967-1970; Yoruba (African people) -- Nigeria -- History; Baptists -- Missions -- Nigeria; Missions -- Nigeria -- History; Baptists -- Missions -- Liberia; Missions -- Africa; Married people in missionary work -- Africa; Children of missionaries -- Africa; Southern Baptist Convention; Southern Baptist Convention. Foreign Mission Board; Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary, Ogbomoso
Contents of Collection
- Correspondence, 1928-1998, (15 boxes)
  The Correspondence series consists of letters sent to and by the Pool family and their relatives, friends, and colleagues. It ranges from 1928-1998 with some undated materials, and with a gap in coverage from 1963-1968. Notable events and correspondence are detailed below, roughly divided by decade.
  Correspondence from 1928 through the 1930s includes a number of letters between J.C. Pool and W.A. Criswell, as well as many between J.C. and Etta H. Pool and between Elizabeth and E.C. and Alice Routh. In 1934 both J.C. and Elizabeth corresponded regularly with Charles Maddry and his secretary Jessie Ford regarding their applications to the Foreign Mission Board of the Southern Baptist Convention and their plans for travel to and service in Nigeria. The letters document their trip to Nigeria in September 1934, and their experience as missionaries, including such events as Elizabeth’s adoption of Gordon on October 27, 1934; J.C.’s breaking his engagement to Faye Winfree in early September, 1935; J.C. and Elizabeth’s courtship and engagement that same month, and their marriage on December 26, 1935; Frances’ birth on Jan. 17, 1937; the death of Lucille and another missionary, Frances Jones, from yellow fever in the summer of 1937; and the Pools’ first furlough in the United States from November 1937-October 1938. The seminary was moved to Oyo in 1937 upon the Pools’ departure, then moved back to Ogbomosho upon the Pool’s return. On June 27, 1938, E.C. Routh received a personal letter from J. Edgar Hoover regarding an article published in the Baptist Messenger, of which E.C. was the editor. Letters from the fall of 1939 and onward discuss WWII and the implications for Americans serving overseas, in both Nigeria and China.
  Correspondence in the 1940s covers Carolyn’s birth on Jan. 24, 1940; the Pools’ furlough in the U.S. from 1941-1943 (the Japanese attack on Pearl Harbor occurred the day the Pools arrived in America and the American entrance into WWII delayed their return by a year); J.C.’s return to Africa in 1943 while Elizabeth and the girls stayed in Oklahoma (the Pools wrote frequently to each other while separated); Elizabeth, Frances, and Carolyn’s return to Nigeria in 1944; the publication of The Hill Called Moon the same year; Jim’s birth on July 29, 1945; the Pools’ 1947-1948 furlough in the U.S.; and Elizabeth’s hospitalization and back surgery in Creek Hospital, Lagos, in 1949, as the African nurses’ and hospital workers’ strike took place. Letters from 1941 concern American missionaries in eastern and southern China in light of the withdrawal of U.S. Marines and letters from the late 1940s discuss the negotiations by which the Southern Baptist Convention and the Southern Baptist Theological Seminary would eventually become affiliated with the Nigerian Baptist Theological Seminary (NBTS) for degree-granting purposes.
  Correspondence from the 1950s covers a number of significant events for the Pool family. A great deal of correspondence from 1950-1951 concerns Copass Routh’s debts and his family’s efforts to make good on them. The Pools went on furlough in America from 1950-1951, at the end of which Frances stayed in America with relatives; after graduating high school in 1953, she enrolled at Baylor, having been granted a scholarship from the Women’s Missionary Union. Claribel Pool married Jonathan Ojeleye December 24, 1953, which caused some controversy due to Claribel and Jonathan’s desire to include Yoruba customs that J.C. and Elizabeth found inappropriate for a Christian ceremony; the two had a child, Funlayo Ojeleye, in Sept. 1954. Elizabeth published a biography of Lucille Reagan in 1954 and The Bead-Maker’s Son in 1957. The Pools again went on furlough in the U.S. from 1954-1955, at the end of which Carolyn stayed in America with relatives. Frances married Robert (Bob) H. Blinn in June 1955; they had Robert (Bobby) in March 1956. Carolyn moved in with Bob and Frances until her graduation from high school in 1958. During that period, Bob, who was in the Air Force, was deployed to Korea in 1957, and the couple had a second son, Keith, in March 1958. Alice Routh died Oct. 24, 1957; the collection includes a number of condolence letters around this time. Family friend and colleague Osad Imasogie married Yewande Akinwumi April 22, 1958 in Nigeria. When the Pools returned to the U.S. on furlough from 1958-1959, they held posts at Southern Baptist Theological Seminary. Carolyn completed her first year of college at the University of Louisville in order to be close to her parents while they served at SBTS, then transferred to Baylor when the Pools returned to Nigeria.
  Correspondence from the 1960s includes letters discussing the establishment of an Foreign Missions Board-funded “M.K” (missionary kids) home in Kentucky with missionaries Neville and Emma Claxon, which opened in Sept. 1960; Jim, who had traveled alone to the U.S. in July, would move into the home when it opened. Claribel and Jonathan had another child, Molara, that same fall, and Katherine Blinn was born to Frances and Bob in June 1961. Gordon married Mary in Dec. 1964. E.C. Routh died in May 1966. Letters from this period also discuss Nigerian independence, the political situation in Africa generally, and Africanization. There is a gap between Aug. 15, 1963 and Nov. 28, 1968, and coverage is generally sparse from Dec. 1961-April 1970.
  Correspondence from the 1970s covers a wide range of events. The Pools went on furlough in the U.S. from 1970-1971, leaving Nigeria for good; Carl Whirley was inaugurated as principal of the NBTS in J.C.’s stead. Jim married Mary in 1970. The Pools returned to Africa in 1971, this time to Mount Nimba Baptist Church in Yekepa, Liberia, where J.C. was the pastor and Elizabeth was the bookkeeper and kept records. Frances had an operation in 1971. Carolyn married Richard Bullington, Jr. Dec. 3, 1971. J.C. Pool was injured in a serious fall early in 1972, prompting hospitalization and a number of letters of sympathy before they finally made the decision to retire in Texas that summer. Jim and Mary had James (Jimmy) in June 1972, and Richard and Carolyn had Richard II in Sept. of the same year. In 1972, Elizabeth was awarded the Distinguished Alumnus Award from the San Marcos Baptist Academy. Bob and Jim were deployed to Thailand in the early 1970s by the Air Force; their service in the Vietnam War had a deleterious effect on their marriages and both Bob and Frances and Jim and Mary began divorce proceedings in 1973. Frances married John Haaren and Jim married a woman named Judy (they would divorce in 1976) and relocated to Hawaii. Bobby Blinn left the Air Force Academy to enter the ministry and married Mary Beth Turkington in the summer of 1977. Carolyn adopted ten-year-old Susan in 1977. In January of 1978, J.C. Pool died. That August, Gordon and his five sons were killed in a car crash in Africa. Porter Routh retired from the Executive Committee of the Southern Baptist Convention in 1979. That same year, Elizabeth traveled to Nigeria to witness the inauguration of longtime friend Osad Imasogie as the principal of NBTS. In addition to these family events, this period includes correspondence (personal letters and formal invitations) between the Pools and the Liberian president, William R. Tolbert, Jr., as well as a discussion of the Udogi policies in Nigeria and efforts to get SBTS to re-certify NBTS degrees after the Nigerian government declared they would no longer enable their recipients to teach.
  Correspondence from the 1980s covers Elizabeth’s 1981 application to the Daughters of the American Revolution, notes from and correspondence regarding Ross Routh’s family genealogy book project in 1982, and Keith Blinn’s marriage to Laura. Several of Elizabeth’s relatives died during this period: Clinton Burnett in Oct. 1985, Copass Routh in Feb. 1987, Ross Routh in July 1987, and Porter Routh in Nov. 1987.
  Correspondence from the 1990s covers Elizabeth’s selection as the University of Mary Hardin-Baylor’s Outstanding Alumna of the Year, Katherine’s marriage to Russ Allison, Gene and his family’s move to Germany, E.C. Routh’s induction into the Oklahoma Baptist Hall of Fame in Nov. 1994, and Carolyn’s participation in an “MK” (Missionary Kids) listserv in 1996, a number of printed emails from which are included in the collection and touch on a number of past and contemporary African issues, including the execution of Ken Saro-Wiwa.
  - Correspondence, 1928 July-1930 Aug. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1930 Sept.-1930 Dec. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1931 Jan.-1931 Apr. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1931 May-1932 Mar. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1932 May-1933 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1934 Jan.-1934 May (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1934 June-1934 Sept. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1934 Oct.-1934 Nov. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1934 Dec.-1935 Jan. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1935 Feb.-1935 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1935 May-1935 June (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1935 July-1935 Aug. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1935 Aug.-1935 Oct. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1935 Oct.-1935 Nov. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1935 Nov.-1935 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1935 Dec. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1935 undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1936 Jan.-1936 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1936 Mar.-1936 Apr. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1936 May-1936 July (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1936 July (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1936 Aug.-1936 Oct. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1936 Nov.-1936 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1936 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
  - Correspondence, 1936 undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1937 Jan. (Box 4, Folder 5-7)
  - Correspondence, 1937 Feb.-1937 Apr. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1937 May-1937 July (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1937 July-1937 Dec. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1938 Mar.-1938 Oct. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1938 Oct.-1938 Dec. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1938, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1930s, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1939 Jan.-1939 Mar. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1939 Mar.-1939 Aug. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1939 Sept.-1939 Dec. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1939, undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1940 Jan.-1941 Jan. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1941 Mar.-1942 Dec. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1943 Feb.-1943 Oct. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1943 Oct.-1943 Dec. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1944 Jan.-1944 July (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1944 July-1944 Dec. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1940s, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1945 Jan.-1947 June (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1947 Sept.-1948 Sept. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1948 Oct.-1949 May (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1949 May-1949 Dec. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1950 Jan.-1950 Dec. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, early 1950s, undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1951 Jan.-1951 May (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1951 May-1952 Jan. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1952 Feb.-1952 Aug. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1952 Sept.-1953 July (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1953 Aug.-1953 Dec. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1954 Jan.-1954 Dec. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1955 Jan.-1955 Sept. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1955 Sept.-1956 Feb. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1956 Mar.-1956 Oct. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1956 Nov.-1957 Aug. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1957 Aug.-1957 Nov. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1957 Dec.-1958 Feb. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1958 Mar.-1958 June (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1958 June-1959 Aug. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1959 Aug.-1959 Dec. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, mid-1950s, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, late 1950s, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1960 Jan.-1960 May (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1960 June-1960 July (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1960 Aug.-1960 Dec. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1961 Jan.-1963 Aug. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1968 Nov.-1971 Jan. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, Mailing lists, 1971-1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1971 Feb.-1971 June (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1971 June-1971 Aug. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1971 Aug.-1971 Dec. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1971 Dec. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1972 Jan. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1972 Jan.-1972 Feb. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1972 Feb. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1972 Mar. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1972 Apr.-1972 May (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1972 June-1972 Dec. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1973 Jan.-1973 June (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1973 July-1973 Dec. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1974 Jan.-1974 Nov. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1975 Jan.-1975 Dec. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1976 Jan.-1976 Dec. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1977 Jan.-1977 Dec. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1978 Jan.-1978 Oct. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1978 Nov.-1978 Dec. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1979 Jan.-1979 Aug. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1970s, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1979 Oct.-1980 Nov. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1981 Jan.-1982 Sept. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1983 Jan.-1985 Nov. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1986 Feb.-1987 Nov. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1988 Jan.-1988 Dec. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1989 Jan.-1990 June (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1990 June-1990 Dec. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1991 Feb.-1991 Dec. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1992 Jan.-1994 Jan. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1994 Apr.-1994 Oct. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1994 Oct.-1994 Dec. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1995 Jan.-1995 Feb. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1995 Feb.-1995 Apr. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1995 May-1995 July (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1995 July-1995 Dec. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1996 Jan.-1996 Feb. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1996 Feb.-1996 Dec. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1997 Jan.-1997 June (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, undated (1939-1998) (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Photographs and Artwork, 1930s-1990s, (5 boxes and 1 oversize folder)